caringtoday.com 2008-05-08

# Caring Today Magazine, LLC Online Privacy Policy | Caring Today

**Caring Today Magazine Online**

Welcome to our site!

The caringtodaymagazine.com Web site (the “Site”) is maintained by Caring Today Magazine, LLC (“CTM,” “us,” “our,” or “we”). Our address is 1465 Post Road East, Westport, CT 06880. We can also be reached by e-mail at [info@caringtoday.com](mailto:info@caringtoday.com). Our data collection and use policies with respect to the Site are set forth in this statement (“Policy”). By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy.

By visiting caringtoday.com, you agree that your visit, and any dispute over privacy, is governed by this Online Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use Agreement. Please take a few minutes to read them before using or registering with our site ** _. Please note that this Privacy Policy applices only to our online collection and use of information and does not apply to any information that you may provide to us by other means, such as via mail or telephone._**

Please read this Online Privacy Policy carefully so that you understand our privacy practices regarding:

**__Children under 13:__**

CTM cares about protecting the privacy of children. We won't knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personally identifying information. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) over the Internet, to us or to anyone else. We encourage you to become involved in your children's online experience, and to share your interest in our site with your young ones. If you're under 13, please do not register with our site or provide us with any personally identifying information (such as your name, your email address or your phone number).

**__Information we collect:__**

The information we gather on our site falls into two categories: (1) information you supply when you register or initiate transactions, and (2) tracking information collected as you navigate through our sites. Third-party providers featured on, or linked to from our site, such as vendors of products and services offered through our site, may gather information, as well.

**__Personally Identifying Information__**

**_Registration Information;_** To use certain features on our site, we ask you to register. When you register, we collect personally identifying information about you, including your name, mailing address, email address, user name and password. We may also ask for some additional information, such as, hobbies, age, browser type, and the like, but you're free to register without providing this information if you prefer. In addition, at various other points on our site, we may ask you for personally identifying information, including when you: subscribe to our magazine, complete a survey, or report a problem with our site. We use this information to process your orders, to tailor our site to your interests and to make them more useful to you, and to help improve our site generally.

**_Contests and Other Promotions;_ **From time to time, we may offer contests or other promotions involving marketing or advertising partners. If you choose to participate in one of these contests or promotions, you'll have to provide some information about yourself (such as your name, address, and email address). We may share this information with sponsors of the contest or other promotional partners, but we will always identify the other parties involved (for example, in the contest rules). We don't control these third parties' privacy practices, and our Privacy Policy does not apply to their collection and use of your information. We urge you to review their privacy policies and learn how they will use your information before participating. If you don't want us to collect the information requested in connection with a promotion, or to provide it to our co-sponsors or partners, please do not participate in the promotion.

**__Tracking Information:__**

**_Cookies;_ **To help us serve your needs better, we use "cookies" to store and sometimes to track user information. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie contains a unique number that allows our sites to identify your computer. For example, cookies allow us to keep track of your user name and password (if you are a registered visitor) so you don't have to re-enter that information each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to make sure you don't see the same ads repeatedly when you visit our site. The help function on most browsers contains information on how to set your browser to notify you before accepting cookies or to disable cookies entirely. However, if you don't accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of various features on our site that are available to other visitors. In addition, our advertising and marketing partners may use their own cookies. 

**_Browser Level Information and IP Addresses;_** When you use our site, we may also collect information about your access time and your computer configuration, including the type of browser software you use, the operating system that you're running, the resolution of your computer monitor and your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers connected to the Internet to identify your computer so that data (such as the web pages you request) can be sent to you. Your IP address does not tell us who you are. Like the IP address, none of the other information described in this paragraph identifies you personally. We collect this information for purposes of aggregated reporting on site activity that we, and our advertisers, may use. For example, we may want to know how long the average user spends on our site, which pages or features get the most attention. The aggregated information helps to understand our audience and confirm the value of advertising on our website.

**__How your information will be used:__**

Our primary goal in collecting information is to provide you with a customized experience when visiting our site and to make our site more valuable to you. 

**_Vendors and Service Providers;_** To make your experience on our site more useful and enjoyable, we may offer some features (such as chat rooms and email newsletters) in conjunction with third party providers ("Provider Partners") that specialize in operating such services. We share with each of these Provider Partners such information as is necessary to provide you with the services we provide you in conjunction with that Provider Partner. Their use of this information will be subject to the terms of their respective privacy policies, which you can find on their websites. _**We will not provide your email address to such third parties unless it's necessary to provide the services you have requested, or to allow you to participate in a co-sponsored promotion.** _

**_Sites to Which We Link;_** We also provide links to other websites, and provide access to products and services offered by third parties, whose privacy policies we don't control. When you access another website or purchase products or services or conduct other transactions through our website, use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the site you're visiting or the provider of such products or services. When you provide information in the course of obtaining products or services through our sites, use of any information you provide may be governed by the privacy policy of the provider of those products or services, even if it appears that you're on our site throughout the transaction. The provider's privacy policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of our providers via a link either from the site's homepage or from the pages on which the products or services are offered, you should contact the provider directly for more information.

**_Subscribing to our magazine;_ **When you are ready to subscribe to our magazine, we will ask you to provide us with certain information, including your contact details (such as your name, address, telephone and email), and your billing information (such as your credit card number and the date that your card expires). We will use the information you provide us to process your transaction and to contact you regarding your subscription if necessary. We will share this information with the relevant merchant to the extent necessary to facilitate your purchase (for purposes such as customer service, verification, fulfillment and billing purposes). We may share non-financial information with such merchants in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**_Postal Address Lists;_** If you provide us with your postal address, we may include that address in postal address lists that we sell or rent to third parties. If you would like us to stop including your postal address in such lists, please send us a letter at Caring Today Magazine, Attention: Website Manager, 1465 Post Road East, Westport, CT 06880, requesting that we remove your postal address from these lists. If we receive such a letter from you, we will act as promptly as possible to remove your postal address from future postal address lists that we sell or rent to third parties.

**_Other Disclosures;_ **We may occasionally release information about our visitors when release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce our Terms of Use Policy or to protect the rights, property or safety of visitors to our sites, the public, or CTM. As our business grows, we may buy or sell various assets. In the unlikely event that CTM, substantially all of our assets, or one or more of our sites (or substantially all of its assets) is acquired by another company, information on our visitors would be among the transferred assets.

**__How to correct or update your information:__**

CTM believes strongly in providing you with the ability to access and edit the personally identifying information that you have provided to us through our websites. To update this information, please visit our My Account area.

**__Newsletters and Promotions:__**

**_Newsletters;_** We may offer you the opportunity to subscribe to email newsletters on various topics that we believe are of interest to our visitors. If you have opted to receive a particular newsletter, you can always unsubscribe later either (1) by following the 'unsubscribe' link located near the bottom of each newsletter, or (2) by going to My Account, selecting "Unsubscribe" from the Newsletter options, unchecking the relevant boxes and pressing the "Update" button.

**_Promotional Emails;_** If you provide us with your email address, from time to time we may send you emails about CTM products, services and special offers (such as special CTM magazine subscription offers) that we believe may be of interest to you. When you register, you will also be given an opportunity to tell us whether you would like to receive emails about products, services and special offers from third-party providers. Though we hope that you will find both types of promotional emails helpful, if you decide that you no longer wish to receive either or both types of emails, email us at [info@caringtoday.com](mailto:info@caringtodaymagazine.com) and we will act as quickly as possible to remove your email address from future promotional emails. 

**__Security:__**

The personally identifying information we collect is stored within a database that we control. We use standard, industry-wide procedures such as firewalls and SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to protect your information. However, as effective as encryption technology is, no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a message you post to any message board, discussion group, or other public posting area on our sites is available to anyone with Internet access. If you don't want people to know your name or email address, for example, make sure not to include it in any message you post publicly. Please see our Terms of Use Policy for more information related to posting materials on our sites, including our use of such materials.

**__Miscellaneous:__**

The Internet is an evolving medium. If we need to change our Privacy Policy at some point in the future, we'll post the changes before they take effect. If you have questions about this Online Privacy Policy, please contact us at [info@caringtoday.com](mailto:info@caringtodaymagazine.com).

Copyright 2004, Caring Today Magazine, LLC

All rights reserved. 

_Effective date: November 1, 2004_
